to me the thing about hari Gameplay is
a mí es que lo de hari Gameplay es una
something that has me crazy and no no
cosa que me tiene loquísimo y no no
I'm talking about a possible new H fan
estoy hablando de un posible nuevo H fan
Ah no no man I'm talking about something that I
Ah no no tío estoy hablando de algo que
don't fully understand let's see if
no termino de comprender a ver si
someone in the audience is able to
alguien en la audiencia es capaz de
explain it to me because maybe it's something that
explicarme porque a lo mejor es algo que
escapes you when you start voting for
se te escapa cuando empiezas a votar a
vascal And the thing is that Ari Gameplay
vascal Y es que Ari Gameplay la semana
last week was uploading stories on
pasada nos estaba subiendo historias en
his Instagram account where he claimed
su cuenta de Instagram donde afirmaba
that he was Healing
que estaba Sanando
[Music]
[Música]
to now suddenly at the moment in
para ahora de repente en el momento en
which he found out that it is Juan
el que se ha enterado que es Juan
Guarnizo his ex-husband who is Healing
guarnizo su exmarido el que está Sanando
but in the big bed with Milica start
pero en la gran cama con milica ponerse
throwing innuendos like a quin añera on his
a tirar indirecta cual quin añera en su
tiktok less than a month less than a
tiktok menos de un mes menos de un
m everything is backwards that I didn't want to fall
m todo me s al revés que no quería
in love
enamorarme
and I am in love I already
y est enamorada Ya me
forgot what
olv qué
Sundays I fell in love with the one I didn't
domingas del que no quería enamorarme me
want to fall in love with and the one I didn't want to fall in love with and the one I was in love with I already forgot this is a phrase that I could have put perfectly in 2005 in  the
puesto Yo perfectamente en el 2005 en el
status of My
estado de Mi
[Music]
[Música]
Messenger and it does not fail when you
Messenger y es que no falla cuando
publish these types of indirect comments like I already
publicas este tipo de indirectas de Ya
forgot you years ago it happened and I will not
te olvidé hace años que ocurrió y no lo
forget it I fell in love with another you do not reach
olvidaré me enamoré de otro no me llegas
the sole of my shoe and this series of
a la suela del zapato y esta serie de
things that you already know the typical ones
cosas que ya sabéis las típicas solo
can only appear to be one thing that is burned
puede aparentar una cosa que está ardida
because Aha Juan is doing his life
porque Aha Juan está haciendo su vida
without crawling for it and yes it
sin estar arrastrándose por ella y sí
is true that she has responded to
que es verdad que ella ha respondido a
a comment to clarify that she is not going after
un comentario para aclarar que no va por
anyone that it is only a Trend
nadie que solamente se trata de un Trend
But you who are watching This video and I
Pero tú que estás viendo Este vídeo y yo
and I also know that nothing on the
y yo también sabemos que nada en
internet is posted by chance
internet se pone de forma casual al
just as it was not true that I
igual que tampoco era verdad que no
had not liked this publication on
había dado like a esta publicación en
Twitter where he criticized that Juan
Twitter donde criticaba que Juan
guarnizo was taking
guarnizo estuviese llevando a la famosa
other girls from olifan to the famous bed What's up
cama a otras chicas de olifan Qué pasa
my kids welcome one more day to the
mi chavalería bienvenidos un día más al
Channel I am Javi oliveira if you did not
Canal Soy Javi oliveira si no me
know me subscribe because here you are going to
conocías suscríbete porque aquí te vas a
find out and we are going to be commenting on all
enterar y vamos a estar comentando todo
the gossip in this video we are going to
el chismes yo en este vídeo vamos a
comment on the new rumors between
comentar sobre los nuevos rumores entre
eh  auron Play and gemita And everything
eh auron Play y gemita Y es que todo
would indicate that auron would have become
apuntaría a que auron le habría cogido
fond of the horns he would even be
cariño a los cuernos incluso los estaría
taking care of them and watering them so that they
cuidando y regando para que cada vez
grow more and more but I also have a
crezcan más pero también tengo
heart so get comfortable And don't
corazón así que ponte cómodo Y no te
miss anything in this video because it's going to be
pierdas Nada de este vídeo porque va a
quite gossipy subscribe
estar bastante chis meante suscríbete
okay mandatory subscribe button do you
vale obligatorio botón de suscribirte
want to browse the
quieres Navegar de forma segura en
internet safely and also access all the
internet y además acceder a todo el
content of your favorite platforms
contenido de tus plataformas favoritas
like Netflix hbo Max or Disney Plus
como Netflix hbo Max o Disney Plus
cyberg VPN And I don't know if you know
cyberg VPN Y es que no sé si lo sabes
but there is content that is not available in your country
pero hay contenidos que en tu país no
and with this little trick
están disponibles y con este truquillo
you can access all the content wherever you
puedes acceder a todo el contenido estés
are I don't know if you know what a
donde estés no sé si sabes lo que es una
VPN is but it is an extension that you put on
VPN pero es una extensión que le pones a
your internet with which it masks the IP and
tu internet con la que enmascara la IP y
apart from browsing completely safely and
aparte de Navegar completamente seguro y
anonymously without anyone being able to know who you
anónimo sin que nadie pueda saber quién
are and where you are It helps you access
eres y dónde estás Te sirve para acceder
some content that is
a algunos contenidos que están
blocked in your country there are movies and
bloqueados en tu país hay películas y
series on your favorite platforms that
series en tus plataformas favoritas que
are not available there are
no están disponibles hay programas de
television programs for example on mediaset
televisión por ejemplo en mediaset
content that if you try to watch them outside
contenidos que si los intentas ver fuera
of Spain they have a geoblock that doesn't
de España tienen un geobloqueo que no te
allows it because with Cyber ​​Ghost VPN that is
lo permite pues con Cyber Ghost VPN eso
over apart from being protected and
se acabó aparte de estar protegido y
browsing anonymously you will be able to
navegando bajo el anonimato podrás
access content from all over the
acceder a los contenidos de todo el
planet you will also have Total privacy
planeta además tendrás privacidad Total
since it keeps your connection private and
ya que mantiene tu conexión en privado y
protects your data Ultra fast speed
protege tus datos velocidad Ultra rápida
to eliminate the lake in any
para eliminar el lago en cualquier juego
online game with which you can enjoy live
online con los que podrás disfrutar de
streams without interruptions and as I have already
directos sin interrupciones y como ya os
told you Freedom to access all the
he dicho Libertad para acceder a todo el
content on the planet wherever and whenever you
contenido del planeta dónde y cuando
want also Take advantage of a whole 83 percent
quieras además Aprovecha todo un 83 por
story using the link that I
de cuento utilizando el enlace que te
leave you in the description of this video and watch out
dejo en la descripción de este vídeo y
because you can try Cyber ​​Ghost VPN
ojo porque puedes probar Cyber Ghost VPN
45 days without obligation and if you are not
45 días sin compromiso y si no te
convinced you ask for a refund and they will give you
convence pides el reembolso y te
back the patza So don't wait any
devuelven la patza Así que no esperes
longer to protect your connection and improve
más para proteger tu conexión y aumentar
your internet experience run
tu experiencia en internet corre enle
click on the link in the description and take
click al enlace de la descripción y
advantage of this super offer cyberghost
aprovecha esta superoferta cyberghost
VPN to browse completely free and
VPN para navegar completamente libre y
safe we ​​continue with the video some of
seguro seguimos con el vídeo alguno de
you have stopped to think that if
ustedes habéis parado a pensar que si
Auro had not caught
Auro no hubiera trincado la cuarta o la
Gemita's fourth or fifth infidelity today instead
quinta infidelidad de gemita hoy en vez
of Gemita being in the situation she
de estar gemita en la situación en la
is in she would surely be one
que está estaría siendo seguramente una
of the most loved girls  of the internet
de las chicas más queridas de internet
living with Auron Play having a
viviendo con auron Play teniendo un
ton of audiences having a ton of
montón de audienci teniendo un montón de
collaborations being hyper meg top I
colaboraciones siendo hiper meg top o
mean how life changes from one movement
sea cómo cambia la vida de un movimiento
to another eh from one day to the next also you
a otro eh de un día para otro además
surely remember that we were
seguramente recordaréis que estuvimos
talking in one of the last videos
hablando en uno de los últimos vídeos
about this topic that Auron and Gemita had been
sobre este tema que auron y gemita
seen together in the Cupra
habían sido vistos juntos en el cupra
attending one of the King Lich events together
asistiendo juntos a uno de los eventos
not only that but Auron allowed
no solamente eso sino que auron permitió
Gemita without any shame to
que gemita sin ningún tipo de vergüenza
start uploading stories on her
se pusiese a subir historias en su
Instagram account from
cuenta de Instagram desde el coche del
Auron's own car so that everyone could
mismísimo auron para que todo el mundo
notice and start speculating and
se diera cuenta comenzase a especular y
leaving many clues so that people
dejando muchas pistas para que la gente
during the afternoon would make it trending on
durante la tarde hiciera trending en
social networks and all the
redes sociales y todos los canales de
gossip channels we would talk speculating if they were
salseo hablásemos especulando si estaban
together if they had gotten back together blah blah
juntos si habían vuelto patatín patatán
Auron at first when people
auron en principio cuando la gente
started commenting on the subject he
empezó a comentarle sobre el tema se lo
took it quite badly and got quite
tomó bastante mal y se puso bastante
rude with people eh but I
borde con la peña eh pero me he dado
realized I mean yesterday I saw the live and
cuenta yo o sea yo ayer vi el directo y
I said [ __ ] Raúl really please
dije [__] Raúl de verdad por favor por
please  It's a little creepy eh And
favor da un poquito de repelus eh Y
friends and people close to me have also told me like, oh no, you
también me lo ha dicho amigos y gente
shouldn't have
cercana en plan [__] no no tendrías
been rude or anything. It's
que haber sido grosero y nada eso sí que
true that I completely agree with you
es cierto que os doy toda la razón en
that I don't have to give explanations about my
que no tengo que dar explicaciones de mi
private life, that's like if tomorrow I
vida privada eso es como si mañana
want to be with seven dwarves and be very
quiero estar con siete enanos Y ser muy
happy. But it's true that the [ __ ] I
feliz pero sí que es verdad que [__] yo
opened the door myself I opened the
mismo Abrí la puerta yo mismo Abrí la
door to this, I don't know if you've
puerta de esto no sé si se os ha
forgotten, but I left it open, I left it
olvidado pero dejó abierta dejó
pending. Better said, the explanation of
pendiente Mejor dicho la explicación de
whether they officially announced their return or
si anunciaban oficialmente la vuelta o
not, practically what they came to
no prácticamente lo que vino a dar a
imply is that they were clarifying their
entender es que estaban aclarando sus
ideas and when they had a decision,
ideas y cuando tuvieran una decisión
then they would explain this. We're
pues ya se explicarían de esto estamos
talking about what's happened. Well, my last
hablando que han pasado pues mi último
video about this was 19 days ago, so they've
vídeo sobre Esto fue hace 19 días o sea
let three weeks go by.
han dejado pasar tres semanas
Now I can't pretend that. Come on, I'm
prácticamente ahora no puedo hacer como
looking the other way. No. It's
que Hala miro para otro lado no No pasa
nothing, so I apologize and I'll give you
nada así que Os pido disculpas y os daré
the corresponding explanations. Well,
las explicaciones correspondientes Pues
in a few weeks when I clarify certain
en unas semanitas cuando aclare ciertas
things that I have to clarify. Because
cosas que tengo que aclarar Porque ahora
right now I'm not clear about anything, nor am I
mismo no lo tengo claro ni yo
at all, so I'll
absolutamente nada con lo cual os
explain it to you.  things when the
explicaré las cosas cuando llegue el
time comes well as I was saying
momento pues como iba diciendo han
three weeks have passed and there is no
pasado tres semanas y ni hay
Reconciliation nor are there more stories in
Reconciliación ni hay más historias en
the car nor is there Auron Play having a
el coche ni hay auron Play teniendo un
redheaded son
hijo pelirrojo
And the thing is that everything would point to the fact that yes Auron
Y es que todo apuntaría que sí que auron
Play is very in love but that's how it looks
Play está mu enamorados pero así se ve
Gemita going to cheat on Auron with up to
gemita yendo a engañar auron con hasta
three different men and then
tres hombres diferentes para luego
playing the victim because I am And the thing is that everything
victimizarse porque lo soy Y es que todo
would point from the clues that
apuntaría por las pistas que ha ido
Auron has been leaving along the way to the fact that
dejando auron en el camino a que las
things this attempt this second attempt
cosas este intento este segundo intento
well third fourth I don't know which attempt
bueno tercero cuarto no sé cuál intento
well would not have turned out as he expected
pues no habría salido como él esperaba
go Auron what a surprise how crazy No I didn't
vaya auron que sorpresa qué loco No no
expect it from anyone or what's new You
se lo esperaba a nadie u qué novedad Me
leave me you leave me all crazy oh oh I don't know
dejas u me dejas toda loca ay ay no me
what crazy unexpected crazy I didn't
lo qué loco inesperado loquísimo no se
expect it from anyone the next thing was
lo esperaba a nadie lo próximo que era
my weapon to think that the peso was going to
mi arma pensar que el peso iba a
help the victims of Dana you
socorrer a las víctimas de la Dana la
would make it from a woman never until I
harías de una mujer jamás hasta que la
see her issue hand apart here wescol lets it
vea tema manita aparte aquí wescol se la
go I have some
suelta tengo unos
fingers that's why the girls come back no
dedos por eso vuelven las chicas no
eh okay I'll give you something I
eh vale a ti te regalo algo a ti te
give you something the thing is that I didn't
regaló algo lo que pasa es que no
understand one  [ __ ] since my
entendió una [__] puesto que tenía la
voice was distorted I have some
voz distorsionada tengo unos
fingers that's it and
dedos eso
a new sipeo has emerged with aurono
esy ha surgido un nuevo sipeo con aurono
attention the handsome guy over there is handsome handsome that's why I did
atención el guapetón de all es guapetón
n't take off my mask I'll
guap eso que no me quit la máscara yo a
see you after this Okay here I
ti te veo después de esto Ok aquí
will
estaré de
agree eh I'm painting myself guys
acuerdo eh Me estoy pintando chicos
When do the
Cuándo empiezan los
games really start you put me in some
juegos de verdad me pones unas
situations for real you make me be one of those over there
situaciones de verdad me pones ser unas
said the hottie over there
de allá dijo el papón de allá
said what the
dijo qué
[ __ ] I'm not eh that's them what he
[__] yo no soy eh que son ellas que lo
said is true I'm
que dijo sí que es verdad yo yo estoy
here quiet silent it's that I'm not I
aquí quieto callado es que yo no soy me
feel intimidated and it's that During the
siento intimidado y es que Durante los
live shows of the last week auron
directos de la última semana auron
would have been dropping some
habría estado dejando caer algunas
clues around there showing his
pistas por ahí demostrando su
discontent with the experiences he's
descontento con las experiencias que ha
had with women
tenido con las mujeres
lately calm down I don't know No no it's that either
últimamente tranquilo no me No no es que
I run into a son of a [ __ ] or I'm
o o me cruzo con un hijo [__] o yo soy
stupid there are two options it's that dumb
tonto hay dos opciones es que tontito
guy on top of throwing my faces [ __ ] stop
tío encima tirarme los jetas [__] para
we've never invited a woman let's see
nunca hemos invitado a una mujer a ver
if we invite a little Cuban I'm that I'm
si invitamos una cubanita Yo es que soy
sexist I'm that I'm sexist you know
machista Yo es que soy machista sabes
that women don't  women should be
que a las mujeres no a mujeres hay que
given pleasure, not hated shut up shut
darle placer no hay que odiarla cállate
up How how women should be given
cállate Cómo cómo la mujer hay que darle
pleasure, not hated But I don't
placer no hay que odiarla Pero si yo no
hate them but I don't want to
las odio pero no quiero
see them you have to understand them you have to
verlas hay que entenderla hay que
understand them
entenderla
simply understand understand their Fury I
simplemente entender entender su Furia
don't have time let's see Barça who
no tengo tiempo hay que ver el Barsa que
are very strong this year damn How
está muy fuerte este año ostia Cómo
are you I'm fine and you're fine well what I
estás Yo bien y tú bien bueno a lo que
came for and long live men the more you
vine y que vivan los hombres entre más
hate women the calmer
odies a las mujeres más tranquilas
we are no Girls no problems a wise man said it a
estamos no Girls no problems lo dijo un
wise man said it no Girls no
sabio lo dijo un sabio no Girls no
problems that's how life works that's how it
problems es así la vida funciona así ya
is but the one that draws the most
está pero la que más ha llama la
attention and the one that seems
atención y la que a mí me parece más
clearest and most convincing to me is this one here is that with
clara y contundente es esta de aquí es
so many lies I'll eat them
que de tanta mentira Ya me me las como
all you'll eat them all you've
todas tú me las como todas tú me he
also eaten Ricky's edit It's not that no no I don't
comido también la de Ricky edit No es
learn you don't learn you don't
que no no no aprendo tú no aprendo tú no
learn Joan it's an incredible thing you're
aprendo Joan es una cosa increíble tú es
that I'll eat even the one of even he's
que me me me como hasta la de hasta
deceiving me Ricky edit you do this already
hasta me engaña Ricky edit tú esto ya
what the [ __ ] is this This is a
qué [__] es esto Esto es una cosa
wonderful thing you already deceived me Ricky edit
maravillosa ya me engañaste a Ricky edit
you happy Dee  cl Rick and Eddy
tú contento Dee cl Rick y Eddy se
invented that for next year there was going to
inventó que para el año que viene iba a
be a Minecraft event similar to
ser un evento de Minecraft l parecido a
the squid games but only
lo de los juegos del calamar pero solo
for Spaniards and it was more than obvious
para españoles y era más que evidente
that it was a joke among its
que era una broma entre sus
participants were people like
participantes se encontraba gente como
Amador Rivas Irene Montero or Kiko Rivera who
Amador Rivas Irene Montero o Kiko Rivera
are characters as well as very
que son personajes así como muy de
fictional No well auron comments that he
ficción No pues auron comenta que él se
fell for this joke
comió esta broma
Hilário the world we have understood how we have
hilário el mundo hemos entendido cóm lo
understood it as I think he
hemos entendido como yo creo que é ha
wanted to understand is that of so many lies I already eat them all you I eat them
querido entender es que de tanta mentira
all you I have also eaten
todas tú me he comido también la de
Ricky's edit It's not It's that no no I don't learn you I don't learn you do
Ricky edit No es Es que no no no aprendo
n't learn Joan it's an
tú no aprendo tú no aprendo Joan es una
incredible thing you are that I eat me
cosa increíble tú es que me me me como
even the one of even he deceives me Ricky
hasta la de hasta hasta me engaña Ricky
edit you this already what the [ __ ] is this This is
edit tú esto ya qué [__] es esto Esto es
a wonderful thing I have already deceived myself
una cosa maravillosa ya me engañé hasta
Ricky edit you several Twitter accounts
Ricky edit tú varias cuentas de Twitter
have come out to give this news like the one you
han salido a dar esta noticia como la
are seeing on screen in
que estáis viendo en pantalla en la
Juanito's account you say bombshell auron
cuenta de Juanito sais bombazo auron
Play separated again from gemita Why Because
Play separado otra vez de gemita Por qué
as for  what was seen were not
Porque como por lo visto no eran
official yet she cheated on him again even if
oficiales aún lo volvió a engañar aunque
you don't believe it according to what
usted no lo crea según lo que comentan
these accounts are saying with these tweets that have
estas cuentas con estos tweets que se
gone viral the situation
han hecho muy virales la situación
after those stories that Gemita
después de esas historias que gemita
took the opportunity to record herself in Auron's car
aprovechó para grabarse en el coche de
Play and get a little bit of cash
auron Play y rascar un poquito de casap
Parneo was a bit such that
parneo fue un tanto tal que
[Music]
[Música]
so in the end it turned out that the person I
así al final resultó que la persona que
liked was using me but I'm
me gustaba me estaba utilizando pero soy
a calm guy and I'm really chill
un tío tranquilo y estoy chill de
about this no proof
[__] sobre esto ninguna prueba
just speculation based on the
solamente especulaciones en base a las
breadcrumbs they've been leaving us
miguitas de pan que nos han ido dejando
like Hansel and Grete so we can get
cual Hansel y Grete para que pillemos
the hints Although everything would fit I
las indirectas Aunque todo cuadraría
also tell you in the last few days there's
también os digo en los últimos días ha
been a rumor about this
habido un rumor por esta historia de
Instagram story in which they assume that Auron
Instagram en la que asumen que auron
could have had a date with Gemita
podría haber tenido una cita con gemita
at the movies because here you can see a
en el cine porque aquí se ve una manga
white sleeve and on another day Gemita had something
blanca y en otro día gemita tenía algo
with a white sleeve or rather
con con una manga Blanca o sea
completely [ __ ] crazy it's pulled
completamente una [__] locura está
out of her ass quite a bit This is worth it
sacado del culo bastante Esto vale
because it could be me in fact
porque podría podría ser yo de hecho
Look it could be me at the
Mira podría ser yo el que está en el
movies with Auron and also Rubén
cine con auron y además Rubén el hermano
Auron's brother has gone  denying some
de auron ha ido desmintiendo algunas
accounts that were sharing This thing
cuentas que estaban compartiendo Esto
about the cinema, [ __ ] and people are commenting
del cine ala madre y la gente comenta
but the photos are not from the same day, no,
pero las fotos no son del mismo día no
no, they were passed to me Well I think she's not
no se me las pasaron Bueno creo que no
answering you, I think that when they went to the
te responde yo creo que cuando fueron al
Cupra they were like that, she must have been there for a few
cupra así estaban habrá estado unas
weeks and then something must have happened again,
semanas y luego otra vez habrá pasado
here one puts it but if she is
algo aquí le pone uno pero si ella está
in Barcelona at least she has a
en Barcelona al menos que tenga una
twin and she is in two different places You
gemela y esté dos lugares distintos Ya
see guys, it wasn't Gemita, it wasn't Gemita,
ven chicos no era gemita no era gemita
eye, but a person comes here below and
ojo pero viene aquí una persona abajo y
says she is in Andorra, she uploaded this this
dice está en andorra esto lo subió esta
morning and yesterday she uploaded a photo of her
mañana y ayer subió una foto de su
kitten Good point because as if, let's see,
gatito Buen punto porque como si a ver
Gemita is not going to be able to go from Barcelona to
gemita no va a poder irse de Barcelona a
Andorra in one day or less bro by car
andorra en un día o en menos bro en auto
eh It won't take long bro Spain is not
eh No tardará mucho bro España tampoco
a big country either, so it is
que sea un país grande entonces sí es
possible that this there are some possibilities
posible que esta hay unas posibilidades
but I want to think not and I think that we
pero yo quiero pensar que no y creo que
all Also we want to think that no, it's
todos También queremos pensar que no
true that yes, yes, it is Gema Auron
verdad es que si si es Gema Ya auron
is already there no no but I want to think that it is not
está no no pero yo quiero pensar que no
what they answer So Auron is not
es qué le responden Entonces auron no
doing Stream because he is
está haciendo Stream porque está
acting as a chauffeur so as not to neglect her
haciendo el de chófer para no descuidar
and leave with another Gemita no no no don't
y que se vaya con otro gemita no no no
say  those things bro I want to think that
no digan esas cosas bro quiero pensar
this can't be happening
que es que no puede estar pasando esto
friends it can't be happening the
amigos no puede estar pasando los
closures are not the same watch out the fact is
cierres no son iguales ojo al dato es
that the photo looks good I swear you only
que la foto se ve bien les juro que solo
see up to here you can't see anything else let's
se ve hasta aquí no se ve nada más vamos
look for the account even auron's that
a buscar la cuenta incluso de auron esta
shares everything
que que comparte todo lo que publica
auron publishes infoauron This is the photo guys
auron infoauron Esta es la foto chicos
what is it no no no you can't draw a
que es que no no no se puede sacar es
conclusion from just this bro and
conclusión a partir de solo esto bro y
people are going crazy saying that it
la gente se está volviendo loca diciendo
's gemita Oh God no no no no I don't
que es gemita Ay Dios no no no no no
want to think that it's not the people who
quiero pensar que no es la gente queé
say Oh well it could be another
dice Ah bueno que puede ser otra otra
streamer now they're going to say it's crisy Nini
streamer ahora van a decir es crisy Nini
but I think she's not even in Andorra anymore
pero creo que ya ni está en andorra
guys put our reliable
chicos pone nuestra Fuente confiable de
Twitter source nauter fy or well now fy says
Twitter nauter fy o bueno ahora fy dice
not that I have to do it but
no es que tenga por qué hacerlo pero
as the biggest gossip account I confirm
como mayor cuenta de salseo os confirmo
100% that auron was not with her at
al 100% que auron no estaba con ella en
the cinema it's not her and
el cine no es ella y le responde el
Auro's brother responds I agree with you
hermano de Auro de acuerdo contigo
Antonio his name is Marcos now this is a
Antonio su nombre es Marcos ya esto es a
meme that nauter frey or well F now
meme de que nauter frey o bueno F ahora
that I had  used to calling her
que ya me había acostumbrado a llamarle
fy that she is actually a man not
fy que ella en realidad es hombre no
something What has caught my attention
algo Alo que me ha llamado la atención
is that Auron's brother has
es que el hermano de auron sí que ha
responded to several accounts that were
respondido a varias cuentas que estaban
sharing this about the cinema
compartiendo esto de lo del cine
denying the Gemita thing basically
desmintiendo lo de gemita básicamente
confirming that it is not emit good
confirmando que no es emita buenos
insults I like Unfortunately you are not
insultos me gustan Por desgracia no
right at all it is not her nor is she going to
aciertas nada no es ella ni lo va a
continue or this other one As you have just
hacer proseguir o esta otra Como acabáis
seen I agree with you Antonio that it is
de ver de acuerdo contigo Antonio que es
Nafay's account denying that this one
la cuenta de nafay desmintiendo que esta
is Gemita okay or so this was
se gemita vale o sea es que esto estaba
also a bit far-fetched but what really
un poco también sacado del culo pero lo
catches my attention is that
que me llama mucho la atención es que el
Auro's brother who is always like
hermano de Auro que siempre está como
giving data not giving us information about
dando datos no dándonos información de
gossip not only during the entire
los chismes no solamente durante toda la
season of last year of
temporada del año pasado del salseo
strong gossip in which he was launching strong direct ind
fuerte que estaba lanzando ind directas
to Carch to Juan Guarnizo to Ari
fuertes a carch a Juan guarnizo a Ari
all these people but now for
toda esta gente sino que ahora por
example also the thing about the horns on his
ejemplo también lo de los cuernos a su
brother We found out because he posted a
hermano Lo supimos porque él puso una
very discreet photo of a goat with
foto muy discreta de una cabra con unos
huge horns Well well it really catches my
cuernos enormes Pues bien me llama mucho
attention that he has been denying
la atención que haya estado desmintiendo
this type of  posts that gemita had
este tipo de publicaciones de que gemita
not gone to the movies with her brother and
no había ido al cine con el hermano y
yet she has not done so with any
sin embargo no lo ha hecho con ninguna
of the viral accounts that are
de las cuentas virales que están
sharing this information, that of
compartiendo esta información la de
Juanito which has 47,000 likes more than 3
Juanito que tiene 47000 likes más de 3
million visits or this other one which
millones de visitas o esta otra que
has 5 million visits with 106,000
tiene 5 millones de visita con 106,000
likes, in other words, this is viral imo and
likes o sea esto está virals imo y sin
yet here he has not denied anything
embargo aquí pues no ha desmentido nada
on his part auron preparing his Prime
por su parte auron preparando su Prime
flirting with girls put it there I
coqueteando con muchachas ponle ahí yo
know the lasagna that is a little spicy but
que sé la lasaña que pique tantito pero
not that sometimes Yes yes I understand something
tampoco que a ves Sí sí entiendo algo
suggestive but not too correct and
sugerente pero no demasiado correcto y
With all due respect in the world of course eh
Con todo el respeto del mundo claro eh
Okay well I think that at this moment I
Okay pues yo creo que en este momento
must be blind because I don't see your
debo de estar ciega porque no veo tu
message telling me that we
mensaje diciéndome que nos
[Music]
[Música]
see each other now one for Aon please like that
veamos ahora uno para Aon por favor así
same one for me please with the
igual uno para mí por favor con con la
same the same level The same level Yes
misma el mismo nivel El mismo nivel Sí
yes you also like something slightly
sí también te gusta algo ligeramente
suggestive Yes yes same level is very
sugerente Sí sí mismo nivel está muy
good your only defect auron is that you don't
bien tu único defecto auron es que no
wake up
despiertas
with me u uyu well damn lucky we
conmigo u uyu bueno [__] suerte le
have  said a clash of salsa valentina
hemos dicho un choque de salsa valentina
[ __ ] if we tell her the whole pot plot
[__] si le decimos todo el bote plot
twist I was rodolfa kangura new achievement
twist yo era rodolfa kangura nuevo logro
unlocked give a personal compliment
desbloqueado hacerle un piropo personal
to auron check Dani from the past who watched
a auron check Dani del pasado que veía
her videos at 14 This was for you It
sus videos con 14 años Esto fue por ti
was a pleasure having served you this
Fue un placer haberte atendido esta
afternoon auron Play I hope your
tarde auron Play Espero que tu
experience enjoying this edition has
experiencia disfrutando de esta edición
been the best my service for now
haya sido la mejor mi servicio por ahora
has ended but I would appreciate it if you
ha terminado pero Te agradecería si
fill out our satisfaction survey
llenas nuestra encuesta de satisfacción
because for my part I had a
porque de mi parte Me la he pasado muy
great time as an added aur Play you have
bien como agregado aur Play la has
followed her Hey this doesn't have to
seguido Oye que esto no tiene por qué
mean anything but since he's supposedly
significar nada pero como supuestamente
back with gemita people are
ha vuelto con gemita la gente anda
speculating auron makes the switch
especulando auron da el cambiazo
losing you're not going to get out for sure uploading
perdiendo no vas a salir seguro subiendo
photos and videos every day in the
todos los días fotitos y vídeos en el
gym with his new workout
gimnasio con su nuevo entrenamiento
[Music]
[Música]
Although I personally think
Aunque yo personalmente pienso que
you have to wait a few
tienes que esperar unos cuantos
months to upload this content that
mesecitos para subir este contenido que
Aha right now an old man stops doing
Aha mismo pare un abuelo haciendo la
rehabilitation that your arm is going to break
rehabilitación que se te va a romper ese
at any moment [ __ ] and
brazo en cualquier momento cabrón y
you family What do you think of all this I
ustedes familia Qué pensáis de todo esto
know that gossip is powerful we'll
sé que el chisme es potente veremos a
see  if they don't give us the icing on the cake between now and
ver si no nos dan la guinda del pastel
Christmas we'll be very
de aquí a las navidades estaremos muy
attentive And as always commenting on
pendientes Y como siempre comentando
everything here is mandatory if you liked
todo aquí obligatorio si te ha gustado
the video like subscribe Comment and
el vídeo like suscribirte Comenta y
all that stuff and we'll see you very soon
todas esas cosas y nos vemos muy pronto
in the next one bye family Goodbye
en el siguiente chao familia Adiós
gorgeous I'm
guapísimos estoy chill de [__] de
really chilled out eh Really people have
verdad eh De verdad la gente se ha
spent the weekend insulting me for
pasado el fin de semana insultándome sin
no reason and I'm really chilled out like it has
ningún tipo de sentido y yo chill de
nothing to do with anything the
[__] en plan nada que ver con nada la
truth
verdad
But if you wanna insult me ​​go ahead I mean I mean like it's
Pero si queréis insultarme adelante o
been
sea quiero decir o sea ha sido
spectacular but people but angry Eh
espectacular pero gente pero enfadada Eh
no eh It's that you're This you're the other thing the same
no eh Es que eres Esto eres lo otro el
old thing eh and I'm like it has
tema de siempre eh y yo en plan es que
nothing to do with anything I mean
nada que ver con nada o
nothing to do with anything but well I've
sea nada que ver con nada pero bueno he
been very calm and very chill eh I'm
estado muy tranquilo y muy chill eh Ya
telling you nothing to do with anything but well
te digo nada que ver con nada pero bueno
that's really chill I am I'm
eso chile de [__] soy soy
literally the dog I'm literally
literalmente el perro soy literalmente
the dog meme eh but but very
el meme del perro eh pero pero muy
calm the heart was unfaithful to me
tranquilo el corazón me fueron infiel
with several girls and and girls sound very
con varias niñas y y niñas suenan muy
bad friend of I didn't want to forgive him but I know
mal amigo de no quise perdonarlo pero sé
that if I come back I will have  the distrust
que si vuelvo tendré la desconfianza de
that he will continue talking to her sounds
que seguirá hablando con suen suena
terrible
fatal
and if I extend the distrust that he
e si vuelvo a tender la desconfianza de
will continue talking to
que seguirá hablando con
more
más
because yes, of course you will always live
pues es que sí claro vas a vivir siempre
like with an anguish with one thing
como con una angustia con una cosa
eh Yes, yes, it is like that but well That depends
eh Sí sí es así pero bueno Eso depende
on you, I am not going to get involved, the truth is, I am
de ti yo no me voy a meter la verdad yo
not going to give you a sermon, I tell you to
no te voy a dar un sermón yo te digo que
do what you want,
hagas lo lo que te salga de los huevos
no In the end it is your life, not your
no Al fin y al cabo es tu vida no tu
life, it cannot be directed eh, your cousin Not
vida no la puede dirigir eh tu primo Ni
someone, not your friend, not your friend in the
alguien ni tu amigo ni tu amiga al fin y
end you should decide but
al cabo lo debes decidir tú pero
eh, complicated, complicated because you always have
eh complicado complicado porque siempre
that anguish there, damn it is going to
tienes esa angustia ahí de [__] va a
happen again, it is going to happen again and if
volver a pasar va a volver a pasar y si
this and if that, Okay, but do what
esto y si lo otro Bueno pero haz lo que
you want, Nicki, I am not going to get involved in that, the
tú quieras Nicki Yo ahí no me meto la
truth is, I am not going to get involved in that, I am not going to get involved in that, the
verdad Ahí no me meto ahí no me meto la
truth is
verdad